The Peter Bekker Papers
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
Peter Bekker Papers
1970-1989
1936-2001
npkmc-239-271
Peter Bekker Jr.
Peter Bekker Sr.
29 Boxes 163 Open Reel Tapes
Peter Bekker Sr. entered the air force in 1944 and became involved in the Far East Network (FEN), an internal radio and television programming station for the U.S. Military. Over the course of 1944 and 1945, Bekker toured Europe with his platoon, documenting the destruction of the war for the FEN. After World War II, Bekker continued his work for the FEN. Over the course of his time in the military, he rose to the rank of Major. While enlisted, Bekker Sr. and his wife had three sons, Peter Bekker Jr., Paul W. Bekker, and Fred Bekker. Junior grew up to become a radio personality himself. Junior wrote, produced, and hosted “On Record” and hosted “Between the Lines”. In the 1990s Junior transitioned his focus and began writing and publishing for magazines on computers. Junior opened a small consulting company, Computer Management Advice, where he helped develop client facing websites, continued to write articles promoting new technologies, and began to write technical manuals for software and hardware. Junior continued this work until the early 2000s. This collection contains materials from both Peter Bekker Sr. and Peter Bekker Jr. These materials encompass both Senior’s and Junior’s careers, and highlight key facets of their professions. The highlight of Junior’s materials is the 163 Open Reel Tapes and the hundreds of cassettes from his radio career.
Marist College Archives and Special Collections 3399 North Road Poughkeepsie, NY Poughkeepsie New York 12601 United States
There are no restrictions on this collection
Peter Bekker Sr. was the descendant of Paul Bekker, an immigrant from Hungary. After graduating from high school, Senior entered the air force in 1944 and quickly became a combat pilot in the Pacific. Senior also became involved in the Far East Network (FEN), an internal radio and television programming station for the U.S. Military. Over the course of 1944 and 1945, Senior toured Europe with his platoon, documenting the destruction of the war for the FEN. After World War II, Bekker was briefly discharged from the military, but quickly reenlisted and continued his work for the FEN. Over the course of his time in the military, Bekker went on to receive multiple college degrees on the GI bill, and rose to the rank of Major. As a Major for the Air Force, Senior continued his work for the FEN. Much of his work focused on developing and planning programming for the FEN. Bekker also pioneered the closed-circuit television system for the FEN.
While enlisted, Bekker Sr. and his wife had three sons, Peter Bekker Jr., Paul W. Bekker, and Fred Bekker. As part of his duty for the FEN, Senior was able to bring his family to live with him in Japan in the late 1950s. While there, Junior attended Japanese schools and was influenced by his fathers work in the television world.
Junior grew up to become a radio personality himself. Attending Lindwood College in St. Louis, Junior became an editor and programming director of his college’s radio station, KCLC. Junior also worked for KMOX, completing two specials on poverty and the Nazi party in St. Louis. After college, Junior went on to work for WCBS as a managing editor. At the same time, Junior wrote, produced, and hosted “On Record”, a bi-weekly album review radio program. Junior also wrote, produced, and hosted “Between the Lines”, a series of 20-part specials that showcased top recording artists such as Barry Manilow, Hall and Oates, and Paul Anka.
Junior continued to grow as a writer, producer, and host on the radio and went on to create more programming, including “In The Microbase”, “Rock Line”, and “Hard News”. Junior opened Cumulonimbus Communications, which started as producing primarily radio programming, but eventually moved on to discovering and producing new music artists, with Mitch Clarvit being one of the most successful artists of Cumulonimbus Communications. Later on, Junior also ventured into the world of TV writing scripts for proposed network television and hosting a news broadcast, CODE 3.
In the 1990s Junior transitioned his focus and began writing and publishing for magazines on computers, including ITC Desktop Magazine and the Microsoft Network. Junior opened a small consulting company, Computer Management Advice, where he helped develop client facing websites, continued to write articles promoting new technologies, and began to write technical manuals for software and hardware. Junior continued this work until the early 2000s.
This collection contains materials from both Peter Bekker Sr. and Peter Bekker Jr. These materials encompass both Senior’s and Junior’s careers, and highlight key facets of their professions. In Senior’s materials, there are documents from his military career, photos from the FEN, and some personal materials. In Junior’s materials, there are documents from his time at CBS, Between the Lines, On Record, and the publishing of books and magazine articles. There are photos from Junior’s careers and vacations, as well as buttons and magnets, clothing, and various other ephemera. The highlight of Junior’s materials is the 163 Open Reel Tapes and the hundreds of cassettes from his radio career.
Communication; Radio; Music; World War II
This collection is organized into two primary series, 1. Peter Bekker Jr. and 2. Peter Bekker Sr. Both of these series are further divided into subseries. In series 1. Peter Bekker Jr. there are 10 subseries, 1.1 CBS Broadcasting, 1.2 Television Broadcasting, 1.3 Music Production, 1.4 Publishing, 1.5 Technical consulting, 1.6 Personal Materials, 1.7 Photos, 1.8 Audio Recordings, 1.9 Electronic Media, and 1.10 Ephemera. In series 2. Peter Bekker Sr, there are X subseries: 2.1 Far East Network, 2.2 Military Documents, 2.3 Correspondence, 2.4 Personal Materials, 2.5 Paul W. Bekker, 2.6 Miscellany, 2.7 Photographs, and 2.8 Ephemera.
Materials were donated by the estate of Peter Bekker Jr. to the Marist College Archives and Special Collections.
No accruals are expected
Materials in this collection may require a cassette player, a mini cassette player, a fidelipac player, an open reel tape player, a ZIP disk reader, or a floppy disk reader to access materials.
- 1. Peter Bekker, Jr.
  - Subseries 1.1 CBS Broadcasting, 1978-1990
    - Subseries 1.1.1 Between The Lines
      - Between The Lines: Paul Anka (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Between The Lines: Hall and Oates (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Between The Lines: Barry Manilow (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Between The Lines General Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Between The Lines Scheduling (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Between The Lines Promotional Folder (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Subseries 1.1.2 On Record, 1978-1985
      - On Record Correspondence, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - On Record Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - On Record Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - On Record Correspondence: Riders in The Sky, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Station Information for On Record (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - On Record Broadcast Schedules, 1978-1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Promotional Campaigns, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - On Record Promos, 1983-1985; Scans of Newspaper Clippings at back of folder (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Clippings About On Record, 1978-1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Byline Magazine, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - On Record Resurrection Pitch, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - On Record Poem and Images, 1979-1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - On Record Master Reel List, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - On Record Photographs: Celebrities (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - On Record Photographs: Peter Bekker (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Subseries 1.1.3 CBS, 1978-1990
      - CBS Correspondence, 1978-1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - General CBS Documents, 1985-1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Sounders for CBS, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - 88 News Headlines and Articles (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - History of WCBS (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - CBS Photographs (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Subseries 1.1.4 CBS Newsroom, 1980-1986
      - John Lennon Death Report and Research, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Associated Press Articles, 1980-1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Associated Press Articles, Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Associated Press Notebooks (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Subseries 1.1.5 Writers Guild, 1975-1988
      - Writers Guild Membership, 1975-1988 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Writers Guild Newsletters, 1982-1987 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Writers Stike Statements, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Writers Stike Newspaper Clippings, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Subseries 1.1.6 CBS Programming Drafts, 1980-1983
      - Music Column Drafts, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Lamba Callaghan TV Script, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Lamba Callaghan TV Script Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Lamba Callaghan TV Script Notes (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 1.2 Television Broadcasting, 1980-1994
  - Subseries 1.3 Music Production, 1980-1982
    - Horace Johnson, 1980 (Box 3, Folder@16)
    - Richard Barron, 1980 (Box 3, Folder@17)
    - Mitch Clarvit, 1982 (Box 3, Folder@18)
    - Rick Mitchell, 1982 (Box 3, Folder@19)
    - Promotional Folders, Undated (Box 3, Folder@20)
  - Subseries 1.4 Publishing, 1982-1998
    - Subseries 1.4.1 Music Books Research, Drafts, and Contracts, 1992-1997
      - The Baroque Era: The Life, Times, and Music Series, 1992; See Box 20 for published version (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - The Story Of The Blues: Life, Times and Music Series, 1993-1997; See Box 20 for published version (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - The Blues Proofs, See Box 20 for published version (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - [Oversized] The Story Of The Blues, See Box 20 for published version See oversized box, folder 1.4.1.28.1 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Broadway: The Life, Times, and Music Series, 1992; See Box 20 for published version (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Country: The Life, Times, and Music Series, 1993; See Box 20 for published version (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Gospel: The Life, Times, and Music Series, 1993; See Box 20 for published version (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Hollywood Music, 1992-1993; See Box 20 for published version (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Mozart: The Life, Times, and Music Series, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - The Romantic Era, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Music Manifests, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Book Proposals, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Notes (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Friedman Correspondence, 1991-1993; Files are copies of pubishing documents (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Friedman Contracts, 1991-1993 (Box 4, Folder 15)
        Please ask staff to provide access to already pulled files. Floppy disk requires reader to access m aterials.
      - Floppy disk, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Subseries 1.4.2 Published Music Books, 1992-1993
      - The Baroque Era: The life, times, and music series, 1600 - 1750, by Peter O.E. Bekker, Jr., 1992; Two copies, See folder 1.4.2.20.1 for CD (Box 20)
      - Big Bands: The life, times & music series by Julie Koerner, 1992; Two copies, See folder 1.4.2.20.1 for CD (Box 20)
      - The Story of the Blues: The life, times, & music series by Peter O.E. Bekker, Jr., 1994; Two copies, See folder 1.4.2.20.1 for CD (Box 20)
      - The Story of the Blues by Peter O.E. Bekker, Jr., 1997; See folder 1.4.2.20.1 for CD (Box 20)
      - Broadway: The life, times, & music series, 1992; Two copies, See folder 1.4.2.20.1 for CD (Box 20)
      - Celebrating Christmas: The life, times & music series by Carol Spier, 1992; Two copies, See folder 1.4.2.20.1 for CD (Box 20)
      - Country: The Life, Times & Music Series by Peter O.E. Bekker, Jr., 1993; Two copies, See folder 1.4.2.20.1 for CD (Box 20)
      - Country by Peter O.E. Bekker, 1993; Two copies, See folder 1.4.2.20.1 for CD (Box 20)
      - Gospel: The life, times, & music series by Peter O.E. Bekker, Jr., 1993; Two copies, See folder 1.4.2.20.1 for CD. Only one CD (Box 20)
      - Mozart: The life, times, & music series by Julie Koerner, 1992; Two copies, See folder 1.4.2.20.1 for CD (Box 20)
      - The Romantic Era, 1992; Two copies, See folder 1.4.2.20.1 for CD (Box 20)
    - Subseries 1.4.3 ITC: Desktop Assessment, 1989
      - ITC: Desktop Assessment Articles, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - ITC: Desktop Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - ITC Launch, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - [Oversized] ITC: Desktop, See Oversized Box, Folder 1.4.3.28.2 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Subseries 1.4.4 Magazine Articles and Drafts, 1996-1998
      - MSN Article: Without A Trace, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - [Oversized] MSN Proof Planning, See Oversized Box, Folder 1.4.4.28.3 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - Microsoft.com magazine, Spring 1998 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - [Oversized] Microsoft.com magazine, Spring 1998; See Oversized Box, Folder 1.4.4.28.4 (Box 4, Folder 24)
      - [Oversized] Microsoft.com magazine, Spring 1998; See Oversized Box, Folder 1.4.4.28.5 (Box 4, Folder 24)
      - [Oversized PC Magazine Proof, See Oversized Box, Folder 1.4.4.28.6 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Subseries 1.4.5 Published Magazine Articles, 1982-1996
      - BME: Broadcast Management Engineering, May-82 (Box 19, Item 1)
      - ITC: Desktop, March-April 1989 (Box 19, Item 2-3)
      - ITC: Desktop, May-June 1989 (Box 19, Item 4-5)
      - ITC: Desktop, July-August 1989 (Box 19, Item 6)
      - ITC: Desktop, September-October 1989 (Box 19, Item 7)
      - Northwest Airlines World Traveler, Aug-92 (Box 19, Item 8)
      - Northwest Airlines World Traveler, Sep-92 (Box 19, Item 9)
      - PC Magazine, 11-Jun-96 (Box 19, Item 10)
      - Microsoft.com Magazine, Preview Issue (Box 19, Item 11-12)
      - Microsoft.com Magazine, Preview Issue (Box 19, Item 13-14)
  - Subseries 1.5 Technical Consulting, 1987-1992
    - Subseries 1.5.1 Computer Management Advice, 1990-1992
      - CBS Restricted Report System, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - CBS Restricted Report System, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      - CBS TechTrak, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - CRP TV Technology, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - PCAP User Manual, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Mt. Sinai, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Sony Music Operations Batch Billing Processor, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Sony Music Northwest Airlines, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Subseries 1.5.2 Other Consulting Agencies, 1988-1998
      - datadROME- COPTS User Manual, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - MPI: Multimeadia, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - MSN: SoHo (Small Office Home Off) Proposal, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - datadROME- CMU Backlog and Production Tracker, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Subseries 1.5.3 INFOCOM Video Game User Manuals, 1987-1988
      - Beyond Zork, 1987 (Box 21, Item 1)
      - Border Zone, 1987 (Box 21, Item 2)
      - Bureaucracy by Douglas Adams, 1987 (Box 21, Item 3)
      - The Lurking Horror, 1987 (Box 21, Item 4)
      - Nord and Bert Couldn't Make Head or Tail of It: Eight tales of cliches, spoonerisms, and other verbal trickery ny Jedd O'Neill, 1987 (Box 21, Item 5)
      - Plundered Hearts by Amy Briggs, 1987 (Box 21, Item 6)
      - Sherlock: The roddle of the crown jewels, 1988 (Box 21, Item 7)
      - Stationfall: Floy is back in the boffoid sequel to planetfall by Steve Meretzky, 1987 (Box 21, Item 8)
  - Subseries 1.6 Personal Materials, 1960-2005
    - Subseries 1.6.1 School, 1960-1975
      - Graded Written Assignments, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Draft Written Assignments, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - ABC Apprenticeship Journal, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - KMOX Radio 1120- Poverty in St. Louis, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - KMOX Radio Stickers (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - St. Charles Journal, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - St. Charles Newspaper Clippings, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Donovan Music (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Subseries 1.6.2 Miscellany, 1970-2005
      - Beechwood Music Corporation Contract, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Belmont Park Tickets (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Biographical Statement and Resume (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Business Cards (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Peter Bekker, Jr. Business and Identification Cards (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - College, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Ellis Island Immigration Certificate (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Home Video Time Indexes (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - KCLC FM Music Lists, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Notes (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Other Correspondence, 1979-2005 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Press Passes and IDs (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - William Bradford (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 1.7 Photos
    - Slides, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Cinema Marque, Belmondo (Sheet 1, Slide 1)
    - Train (Sheet 1, Slide 2)
    - X-rated film posters (Sheet 1, Slide 3)
    - Arc de Triumphe, road (Sheet 1, Slide 4)
    - Arc de Triumphe, road (Sheet 1, Slide 5)
    - Relief Sculpture (Sheet 1, Slide 6)
    - Architectural ceilings, [Notre dame?] (Sheet 1, Slide 7)
    - Burger king sign (Sheet 1, Slide 8)
    - Landscape (Sheet 1, Slide 9)
    - Town with large mountain in background (Sheet 1, Slide 10)
    - Village [Germany?] (Sheet 1, Slide 11)
    - Village [Germany?] (Sheet 1, Slide 12)
    - Family at table (Sheet 1, Slide 13)
    - Breakfast table (Sheet 1, Slide 14)
    - Television (Sheet 1, Slide 15)
    - Bathroom (Sheet 1, Slide 16)
    - Bedroom [Hotel?] (Sheet 1, Slide 17)
    - Building at night (Sheet 1, Slide 18)
    - People walking down street at night (Sheet 1, Slide 19)
    - Marquee, Kolner City (Sheet 1, Slide 20)
    - McDonalds Menu (Sheet 2, Slide 1)
    - Burger King Menu (Sheet 2, Slide 2)
    - People in car, shot through front of windshield (Sheet 2, Slide 3)
    - Military tower (Sheet 2, Slide 4)
    - City street at night (Sheet 2, Slide 5)
    - Mountain landscape (Sheet 2, Slide 6)
    - Town with large mountain in background (Sheet 2, Slide 7)
    - Child on sled (Sheet 2, Slide 8)
    - Snowy village (Sheet 2, Slide 9)
    - Ancient village (Sheet 2, Slide 10)
    - Pasture (Sheet 2, Slide 11)
    - Train (Sheet 2, Slide 12)
    - Train window (Sheet 2, Slide 13)
    - Mountain, looking over roof (Sheet 2, Slide 14)
    - Train (Sheet 2, Slide 15)
    - Man with headphones on train (Sheet 2, Slide 16)
    - Snowy village, aerial (Sheet 2, Slide 17)
    - Snowy village, aerial (Sheet 2, Slide 18)
    - Snowy village, aerial (Sheet 2, Slide 19)
    - Snowy village, aerial (Sheet 2, Slide 20)
    - Snowy village, aerial (Sheet 3, Slide 1)
    - Snowy village, aerial (Sheet 3, Slide 2)
    - Peter Bekker standing on mountain top (Sheet 3, Slide 3)
    - Snowy mountain top (Sheet 3, Slide 4)
    - Rail tracks on mountain (Sheet 3, Slide 5)
    - Snowy mountain top (Sheet 3, Slide 6)
    - Train conductor (Sheet 3, Slide 7)
    - City street at night (Sheet 3, Slide 8)
    - Trains (Sheet 3, Slide 9)
    - Clothing shop display (Sheet 3, Slide 10)
    - Band playing, restaurant (Sheet 3, Slide 11)
    - Living Room (Sheet 3, Slide 12)
    - Vostra sign (Sheet 3, Slide 13)
    - Mountain top (Sheet 3, Slide 14)
    - Peter Bekker on Boat (Sheet 3, Slide 15)
    - Dock at night (Sheet 3, Slide 16)
    - Harbor entrance (Sheet 3, Slide 17)
    - Covering from sun (Sheet 3, Slide 18)
    - Teenager in front of large wooden door (Sheet 3, Slide 19)
    - Large crucifix (Sheet 3, Slide 20)
    - Church in front of mountain (Sheet 4, Slide 1)
    - Church alter (Sheet 4, Slide 2)
    - Violins (Sheet 4, Slide 3)
    - Person working in front of window (Sheet 4, Slide 4)
    - Building, mountain in background (Sheet 4, Slide 5)
    - Peter Bekker on boat (Sheet 4, Slide 6)
    - City street, clock tower (Sheet 4, Slide 7)
    - Peter Bekker on train (Sheet 4, Slide 8)
    - Large cat in cage [zoo?] (Sheet 4, Slide 9)
    - Marble statue (Sheet 4, Slide 10)
    - Woman selling eggs on street (Sheet 4, Slide 11)
    - Street market (Sheet 4, Slide 12)
    - Large cat in cage [zoo?] (Sheet 4, Slide 13)
    - Statue (Sheet 4, Slide 14)
    - Peter Bekker, city in background (Sheet 4, Slide 15)
    - Pier (Sheet 4, Slide 16)
    - Two women walking on wooden pathway (Sheet 4, Slide 17)
    - Building (Sheet 4, Slide 18)
    - Venice (Sheet 4, Slide 19)
    - Venice (Sheet 4, Slide 20)
    - Venice (Sheet 5, Slide 1)
    - Venice (Sheet 5, Slide 2)
    - Boat (Sheet 5, Slide 3)
    - Two men, one eating pasta [Chef and a celebrity?] (Sheet 5, Slide 4)
    - Two men, one eating pasta [Chef and a celebrity?] (Sheet 5, Slide 5)
    - Two men, one eating pasta [Chef and JFK] (Sheet 5, Slide 6)
    - Angel statue (Sheet 5, Slide 7)
    - Statue in church (Sheet 5, Slide 8)
    - Man with horses (Sheet 5, Slide 9)
    - Street market (Sheet 5, Slide 10)
    - Bay (Sheet 5, Slide 11)
    - Bay (Sheet 5, Slide 12)
    - Mountain (Sheet 5, Slide 13)
    - City square, flooded (Sheet 5, Slide 14)
    - City square, flooded, wooden pathway running over water (Sheet 5, Slide 15)
    - Seaside city (Sheet 5, Slide 16)
    - Sign, "Keep Exit Clear" (Sheet 5, Slide 17)
    - Man drinking beer (Sheet 5, Slide 18)
    - People walking on wood platform over flooded streets (Sheet 5, Slide 19)
    - Skylights (Sheet 5, Slide 20)
    - City square, church in background (Sheet 6, Slide 1)
    - Harbor at sunset (Sheet 6, Slide 2)
    - Harbor at sunset (Sheet 6, Slide 3)
    - Street market (Sheet 6, Slide 4)
    - Horses on street (Sheet 6, Slide 5)
    - Peter Bekker next to Abbey Road sign (Sheet 6, Slide 6)
    - Abbey Road Studios sign (Sheet 6, Slide 7)
    - Bar scene (Sheet 6, Slide 8)
    - Air plane wing (Sheet 6, Slide 9)
    - Graffiti, "USA=VIETNAM LIB" (Sheet 6, Slide 10)
    - Graffiti, "VIETNAM LIBERO" (Sheet 6, Slide 11)
    - Painting, close up (Sheet 6, Slide 12)
    - Poster, "Members concerned with Japanese Red Army" (Sheet 6, Slide 13)
    - Police officers (Sheet 6, Slide 14)
    - Convent on top of hill (Sheet 6, Slide 15)
    - Painted ceiling (Sheet 6, Slide 16)
    - Hotel room, view of bathroom (Sheet 6, Slide 17)
    - Church dome (Sheet 6, Slide 18)
    - Train/Bus (Sheet 6, Slide 19)
    - Man working on manhole cover (Sheet 6, Slide 20)
    - Man working on tram lines (Sheet 7, Slide 1)
    - Man working on tram lines (Sheet 7, Slide 2)
    - Man on train (Sheet 7, Slide 3)
    - Landscape (Sheet 7, Slide 4)
    - City street (Sheet 7, Slide 5)
    - Woman in front of grand building (Sheet 7, Slide 6)
    - Train station (Sheet 7, Slide 7)
    - Man in cabin, [train?] (Sheet 7, Slide 8)
    - Photo of framed picture, woman (Sheet 7, Slide 9)
    - Sail boats on bay (Sheet 7, Slide 10)
    - Sail boats on bay (Sheet 7, Slide 11)
    - Marina (Sheet 7, Slide 12)
    - T-shirt (Sheet 7, Slide 13)
    - Lisense plate, Monaco (Sheet 7, Slide 14)
    - Grand building, palm trees (Sheet 7, Slide 15)
    - Peter Bekker drinking beer (Sheet 7, Slide 16)
    - Group drinking beer (Sheet 7, Slide 17)
    - Television (Sheet 7, Slide 18)
    - Eiffel tower (Sheet 7, Slide 19)
    - Train station (Sheet 7, Slide 20)
  - Subseries 1.8 Audio Recordings, Cassettes are organized alphabetically
    - Subseries 1.8.1 Cassettes
      - [Afrika] Steely Dan / Afrika, Artist: Afrika Length: 01:31:31 Type: Music File Names: 1.7.1.11.1.mp3, 1.7.1.11.1.wav (Box 11, Cassette 1)
      - [Alabama] Gene Simmons /Nona Hendry x Blotto /Alabama, Artist: Alabama Length: 01:24:43 Type: Interview File Names: 1.7.1.11.2.mp3, 1.7.1.11.2.wav (Box 11, Cassette 2)